https://www.mpipressure.com/mpi-melt-pressure-privacy-policy

Melt Pressure Transducers & Transmitters
Melt Pressure Transducers - Standard (mV/V)
Melt Pressure Transmitters - Standard (mA or V)
NaK Fill – Melt Pressure Transducers & Transmitters (mV/V, mA or V)
Oil Fill - Melt Pressure Transducers / Transmitters (mV/V, mA or V)
Melt Pressure Transmitters - SIL2 - 4-20mA with Remote and Local Zero
Digital Indicators
Pressure (Strain Gauge)
MPI Melt Pressure Privacy Policy
Effective: January 1, 2017MPI Melt Pressure is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to our web site and will not sell or provide any non-public personal information to anyone without your permission. Types of Information Cookies. A Cookie is a randomly generated unique number placed on your computer. It allows us to identify your computer without requiring your disclosure of any Non-Public Personal Information. Cookies make it possible to both store and retrieve information through your internet browser. A Cookie itself cannot read information off a hard drive or read Cookie files from other sites.General Information is information that does not itself reveal your identity. General Information may include, without limitation: generic business type; SIC code; information derived from publicly available databases (such as Dun and Bradstreet); user behavior on our Web site; and aggregated generic information. Non-Public Personal Information is any non-public information you provide to us or our Partners that is proprietary or identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate you or someone at your business. Non-Public Personal Information may include, without limitation: name; address; phone number; e-mail address; credit card number; account information; voting behavior; spending patterns; and individual tastes and preferences. Partners are individuals or entities we engage to help us carry out our mission.  What Information We CollectMPI Melt Pressure collects general information and non-public personal information.How We Collect Our InformationMPI Melt Pressure collects our general information through the use of cookies and server-based tracking systems to view the usage of the website.Non-public personal information is collected through registration or contact forms on this site and will never be used for any purpose other than internal use or by our partners unless the registrant chooses to be added to mailing lists (this is a choice made by the registrant on the Registration form). Privacy Policy ChangesAny changes to this privacy policy will be posted here and unless otherwise noted on our website.Changing Your Non-Public Personal InformationMPI Melt Pressure provides you with the opportunity to change your non-public personal information online for all registration information. Please contact MPI Melt Pressure to change any non-public personal information provided to us through a contact form. MPI carries a complete line of melt pressure products, including melt pressure transducers, melt pressure transmitters, melt pressure cables, connectors, hole plugs, hole drill kits, and hole clean kits.Request further info on MPI Melt Pressure privacy policy. Contact MPI to learn more.
Melt Pressure Products
Melt Pressure Transducers & Transmitters
Melt Pressure Transducers - Standard (mV/V)
Melt Pressure Transmitters - Standard (mA or V)
NaK Fill – Melt Pressure Transducers & Transmitters (mV/V, mA or V)
Oil Fill - Melt Pressure Transducers / Transmitters (mV/V, mA or V)
Melt Pressure Transmitters - SIL2 - 4-20mA with Remote and Local Zero
Transducers, Transmitters,
Melt Pressure Transducers - Standard (mV/V)
Melt Pressure Transmitters - Standard (mA or V)
NaK Fill – Melt Pressure Transducers & Transmitters (mV/V, mA or V)
Oil Fill - Melt Pressure Transducers / Transmitters (mV/V, mA or V)
Melt Pressure Transmitters - SIL2 - 4-20mA with Remote and Local Zero
Pressure (Strain Gauge)
97-170 Brockport Dr.
